export default data7 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "Which flower is associated with Scotland?",
        options: ["The Shamrock", "The Rose", "The Daffodil", "The Thistle"],
        correct_option: "The Thistle"
    },
     {
        id: "q2",
        question: "World War II started as a result of Germany invading which country?",
        options: ["France", "Russia", "Poland", "Austria"],
        correct_option: "Poland"
    },
     {
        id: "q3",
        question: "Police complaints can only be made by writing to the Chief Constable of the police force involved.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q4",
        question: "Which of the following is a responsibility of the Home Secretary?",
        options: ["Economy", "Crime", "Education", "Defence"],
        correct_option: "Crime"
    },
     {
        id: "q5",
        question: "When is St David’s day celebrated?",
        options: ["1st March", "17th March", "23rd April", "17th April"],
        correct_option: "1st March"
    },
     {
        id: "q6",
        question: "What happened to ‘Mary, Queen of Scots’ after she spent 20 years in prison?",
        options: ["She became Queen of England", "She was sent to France", "She escaped to Denmark", "She was executed"],
        correct_option: "She was executed"
    },
     {
        id: "q7",
        question: "How many national parks are there in England, Wales and Scotland?",
        options: ["25", "15", "18", "42"],
        correct_option: "15"
    },
     {
        id: "q8",
        question: "Is Northern Ireland part of Great Britain?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        correct_option: "No"
    },
     {
        id: "q9",
        question: "What day relates to the death of Jesus Christ?",
        options: ["Good Friday", "Easter Sunday", "Easter Monday", "Ash Wednesday"],
        correct_option: "Good Friday"
    },
     {
        id: "q10",
        question: "Who is the heir to the throne of Britain?",
        options: ["The Prince of Wales", "The Prince of Cambridge", "The Prince of Edinburgh", "The Duke of York"],
        correct_option: "The Prince of Wales"
    },
     {
        id: "q11",
        question: "What was achieved with the Carta Magna?",
        options: ["It restricted the King's power", "It increased the King's power", "It restricted the rights of the farmers", "It increased women's power"],
        correct_option: "It restricted the King's power"
    },
     {
        id: "q12",
        question: "What year were women given the right to vote?",
        options: ["1918", "1925", "1949", "1914"],
        correct_option: "1918"
    },
     {
        id: "q13",
        question: "Who did the English defeat in 1588?",
        options: ["The Normands", "The Romans", "The Spanish Armada", "The Saxons"],
        correct_option: "The Spanish Armada"
    },
     {
        id: "q14",
        question: "Who designed the Cenotaph?",
        options: ["Sir Norman Foster", "Lancelot ‘Capability’ Brown", "Sir Edwin Lutyens", "Isambard Kingdom Brunel"],
        correct_option: "Sir Edwin Lutyens"
    },
     {
        id: "q15",
        question: "How often are the members of the Welsh government elected?",
        options: ["Every 5 years", "Every 2 years", "Every 4 years", "Every 3 years"],
        correct_option: "Every 4 years"
    },
     {
        id: "q16",
        question: "During which period did the Beatles become popular and social laws were liberalised?",
        options: ["1960s", "1970s", "1980s", "1950s"],
        correct_option: "1960s"
    },
     {
        id: "q17",
        question: "The Man Booker Prize is awarded in which of the following categories?",
        options: ["Films", "Sport", "Literature", "Music"],
        correct_option: "Literature"
    },
     {
        id: "q18",
        question: "What sort of election takes place when a member of the Parliament (MP) dies or resigns?",
        options: ["Coalition", "Pre-selection", "Random selection", "By-election"],
        correct_option: "By-election"
    },
     {
        id: "q19",
        question: "What is the Turner Prize?",
        options: ["A literature award", "A music award", "A contemporary art award", "A theatre award"],
        correct_option: "A contemporary art award"
    },
     {
        id: "q20",
        question: "How old do you need to be to be able to play the National Lottery?",
        options: ["16 years old", "18 years old", "20 years old", "21 years old"],
        correct_option: "18 years old"
    },
     {
        id: "q21",
        question: "Where is the five-day race meeting attended by members of the Royal Family and known as Royal Ascot celebrated?",
        options: ["In Luton", "In Berkshire", "In Salisbury", "In Kent"],
        correct_option: "In Berkshire"
    },
     {
        id: "q22",
        question: "Who was the first person to lead a Roman invasion in Britain in 55 BC?",
        options: ["Emperor Claudius", "Julius Caesar", "Napoleon", "William Caxton"],
        correct_option: "Julius Caesar"
    },
     {
        id: "q23",
        question: "Who wrote ‘ The Lord of the Rings’?",
        options: ["JK Rowling", "JRR Tolkien", "Sir William Golding", "Jane Austen"],
        correct_option: "JRR Tolkien"
    },
     {
        id: "q24",
        question: "Which court deals with minor criminal cases in England, Wales and Northern Ireland?",
        options: ["The Justice of the Peace Court", "The Magistrates’ Court", "The High Court", "The Crown Court"],
        correct_option: "The Magistrates’ Court"
    }
]